distinctathlete.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Distinct Athlete

[Home](http://distinctathlete.com/) Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Distinct Athlete will never sell our integrity. Just as importantly, Distinct Athlete will never rent, share, or sell our subscriber list. We appreciate you letting us into your email, and we promise not to abuse that trust. We make this promise because we understand just how much you value your privacy. The policy below describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our site and/or register for Distinct Athlete. Please read this carefully. There will not be a test, but it’s still important.

#### Your Information

We’re not interested in obtaining a list of your past girlfriends, political affiliations, or the shady things you’ve done for money. All we need is your email address. Distinct Athlete doesn’t collect any information except that expressly provided by you. We will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, except as required to provide you with Distinct Athlete material.

#### Other Information

In order to make our site better, we may also request other information from you. Just generic stuff — like income level or age, that will help us tailor the site to your needs. We may also share this information with third parties, but only in aggregate, anonymous form.  No third party will receive information from us that personally identifies you or anyone else in any way.

#### Usage Information

It is important for us to gather information on how our site is used: How much time do users spend on our site? What sites did they come from? What sites do they go to once they’ve had just about enough of our material? All of this information is collected in aggregate form. None of it is personally identifiable. This information will not make it possible for us to corner the market on, say, frozen concentrated orange juice. It’s collected only to help us to, among other things, handle traffic on Distinct Athlete, and to make sure that our service reaches you in the most efficient manner possible.

#### Review and Access

If you request it, Distinct Athlete will provide you with a summary of the information we’ve collected about you, and the opportunity to correct, update or modify this information.

#### How to Unsubscribe

You can unsubscribe from receiving Distinct Athlete emails at any time. You can unsubscribe by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link in the footer of any Distinct Athlete email and following the instructions.

#### Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by Google, our Web advertising partner. View Google’s privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/privacy.html).

Occasionally, you’ll get an email marked “Sponsored” in the subject line and in the email header. These emails are not necessarily reflective of the opinions of our editorial staff. They are content paid for by our sponsors, and only reflect the fact that our editorial staff has to put food on the table just like everybody else. Some of this money might also go towards alcohol, but we’re not saying how much.

You can unsubscribe from receiving Allied Info emails. However, if you do so, you will no longer receive Distinct Athlete emails either. You can unsubscribe by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link in the footer of any Distinct Athlete email and following the instructions.

#### Cookies

Back in the day, a “cookie” was either something you ate, or a monumentally grating term of endearment. In Internet terminology, cookies are small text files placed on your computer, in order to help websites like ours retrieve information vital to providing the best possible service. Our cookies allow us to recognize you and simplify your user experience. Distinct Athlete will never use cookies to obtain any information from your computer not related to our site.

#### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

#### Links to Other Sites

Distinct Athlete loves using links. Partly because they allow us to guide you towards valuable products and services, and partly because there’s a lot of really weird garbage out there, and exposing you to it is extremely pleasurable. However, we are not responsible for any content that appears on these sites, nor do we endorse them. For questions about these sites, please consult their individual privacy policies.

#### Security

All of the information described above is recorded on embossed sheets of gold leaf locked in steel vaults thousands of feet beneath the earth’s crust, or on our secure server.

#### Modifications

Distinct Athlete may make changes to this policy in the future. Not wholesale changes, like “Privacy? Forget that noise!” Just modifications. If and when we do, we’ll be sure to inform you here.

#### Contact Us

If you have questions about this policy, or about the site, please contact us or you could also review our [FAQ](http://distinctathlete.com/faq) page.
